Guide to the Office of Cultural Affairs Records, 1931-2002 (bulk 1958-2002)
Duke University. University Archives
- Duke Artists Series, 1931-2002, (2 boxes)
  - 1984-1985 Season
    - North Carolina Dance Theater, 1984 Sept. 20-21 (Box 7)
    - San Francisco Western Opera Theater, 1984 Oct. 25 (Box 7)
    - James Galway, 1984 Nov. 1 (Box 7)
    - Vladimir Ashkenzay, 1985 Jan. 22 (Box 7)
    - Rotterdam Philharmonic Orchestra, 1985 Feb. 21 (Box 7)
    - New York Chamber Soloists, 1985 Mar. 21 (Box 7)
  - 1985-1986 Season
    - Benefits--Friends of Duke Artists Series, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
    - Reports, including ticket prices, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
    - Lynn Harrell, 1985 Oct. 1 (Box 7)
    - Pinchas Zukerman, 1985 Nov. 19 (Box 7)
    - Hungarian State Symphony, 1985 Dec. 2 (Box 7)
    - The Crucible, 1986 Jan. 9-12 (Box 7)
    - Lar Lubovitch, 1986 Feb. 6 (Box 7)
    - Kiri Tekanawa, 1986 Apr. 5 (Box 7)
    - St. Louis Symphony, 1986 Apr. 17 (Box 7)
  - 1986-1987 Season
    - Cosi Fan Tutte, 1986 Sept. 24 (Box 7)
    - Ruth Laredo, 1986 Nov. 18 (Box 7)
    - BBC Symphony, 1987 Jan. 14 (Box 7)
    - Jorma Hynninen, 1987 Feb. 5 (Box 7)
    - Emanuel Ax and Yo-Yo Ma, 1987 Mar. 30 (Box 7)
    - Issac Stern, 1987 Apr. 9 (Box 7)
  - 1987-1988 Season
    - Barber of Seville, 1987 Sept. 30 (Box 7)
    - Murray Perahia, 1987 Oct. 27 (Box 7)
    - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, 1988 Feb. 2 (Box 7)
    - Rostropovich, 1988 Feb. 14 (Box 7)
    - Gregg Smith Singers, 1988 Mar. 14 (Box 7)
    - Philharmonia Orchestra--cancellation, 1987 Mar. 15 (Box 7)
    - Swedish Radio Orchestra (cancelled) and Lin, Cho-Liang, 1988 Mar. 29 (Box 7)
    - Canadian Brass, 1988 Apr. 20 (Box 7)
  - 1997-1998 Season (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
    - Frederica von Stade, 1997 Oct. 8 (Box 8)
    - Houston Ballet, 1997 Nov. 1-2 (Box 8)
    - Kings Singers, 1998 Jan. 29 (Box 8)
    - Berlin Symphony, 1998 Feb. 22 (Box 8)
    - Simon Boccanegra, 1998 Mar. 6, 8 (Box 8)
    - Jon Kimura Parker, 1998 Apr. 1-2 (Box 8)
  - 1998-1999 Season
    - Boys Choir of Harlem, 1998 Oct. 4 (Box 8)
    - St. Petersburg State Symphony Orchestra, 1998 Nov. 8 (Box 8)
    - Lynn Harrell, 1999 Jan. 29 (Box 8)
    - Chorovaya--Russian Male A Cappella Chorus, 1999 Mar. 2 (Box 8)
    - Murray Perahia, 1999 Apr. 3 (Box 8)
  - 1999-2000 Season
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
    - Midori, 1999 Oct. 14 (Box 8)
    - Denyce Graves, 1999 Nov. 8 (Box 8)
    - Academy of St. Martin in the Fields, 2000 Feb. 28 (Box 8)
    - Alicia de Larrocha, 2000 Mar. 22 (Box 8)
    - Luyala--dance opera in three acts, 2000
      - Final report, 2000 Apr. (Box 8)
      - Press materials, photographs, slides, and other materials, 2000 Mar. 31-Apr. 1, (3 folders) (Box 8)
      - Luyala, Act One (TRT 52:15) and Luyala, Acts Two/Three (TRT 1:09:40), 2000 Apr. 1, (2 VHS videocassettes) (Box 8)
      - Luyala, Act I and Luyala, Acts II/III, DAT masters and copies for two performances, 2000 Mar. 30 and Apr. 1, (8 digital audio tapes) (Box 8)
      - Audiocassettes (analog), unlabeled and undated, (4 cassettes) (Box 8)
- Summer Session, 1964-2002, (2 boxes)
  Records about the special scheduling of summer events on campus, including Artsfare (later Summer Festival of the Arts), the Loblolly Summer Performing Arts Festival, and Summer Theatre at Duke. Materials include approximately 100 black-and-white and color photographs and 35mm slides. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Artsfare, 1978-1985, (11 folders) (Box 9)
    Annual summer arts festival; in 1986 the name was changed to Summer Festival of the Arts, and continuing records are filed under that name.
  - Correspondence, 1976-1984 (Box 9)
  - Financial statements, 1978-1982 (Box 9)
  - Loblolly Summer Performing Arts Festival, 1975-1978, (6 folders) (Box 9)
  - Loblolly Summer Performing Arts Festival--advisory committee, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Loblolly Summer Performing Arts Festival--photographs, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Position paper on summer session, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Printed material, 1971-1992, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Program Planning Committee, 1972 (Box 9)
  - Robinson, Schuyler, 1972-1974 (Box 9)
  - Summer Dance Program, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Summer entertainment, 1964-1978, (6 folders) (Box 9)
  - Summer Festival of the Arts, 1986-2002, (19 folders) (Box 9)
    See Artsfare, above, for similar records filed under the Festival's earlier name.
  - Summer session, 1988-1990, (6 folders) (Box 9)
  - Summer Theater at Duke, 1978-1984, (2 folders) (Box 9)
- Triangle Dance Guild, 1975-1984, (2 boxes)
  Documents Duke's involvement with the Triangle Dance Guild from the late 1970s through the early 1980s. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Alvin Ailey Repertory Ensemble, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Articles and by-laws, 1976-1984 (Box 10)
  - Atlanta Ballet, 1976-1978 (Box 10)
  - Betty Jones--"Dances We Dance," 1976 (Box 10)
  - Bill Evans Dance Company, 1976-1978 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 10)
  - Dan Wagoner and Dancers, 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - Financial statements, 1976-1980 (Box 11)
  - Grants, 1976-1981 (Box 11)
  - Kathryn Posin Dance Company, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
  - Lar Lubovitch Dance Company, 1980-1981 (Box 11)
  - Lotte Gansler's Pantomime Circus, 1975-1977 (Box 11)
  - Meeting minutes, 1976-1982 (Box 11)
  - "Midsummer Night's Dream" Film, 1976-1978 (Box 11)
  - Milwaukee Ballet, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
  - Mimi Garrard Dance Theatre, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Murray Louis Dance Company, 1980 (Box 11)
  - North Carolina Dance Theater, 1976-1981, (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Oakland Ballet, 1980-1982 (Box 11)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Pauline Koner Dance Consort, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theater, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Printed material, 1975-1981 (Box 11)
  - Washington Ballet, 1979-1980 (Box 11)